{
    "subject": "resource/Cycling_at_the_1992_Summer_Olympics_\u2013_Men's_team_time_trial",
    "predicate": "ontology/goldMedalist",
    "object": "resource/Michael_Rich_(cyclist)",
    "human_readable": "Michael Rich was the gold medalist in the men's team time trial cycling event at the 1992 Summer Olympics.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9855485558509827,
            "question": "Who won the gold medal in the men's team time trial cycling event at the 1992 Summer Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9761038422584534,
            "question": "Was Michael Rich part of a team that won a gold medal at the 1992 Summer Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9131525158882141,
            "question": "In what sport did Michael Rich compete in the 1992 Summer Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8708584904670715,
            "question": "What event did Michael Rich win a gold medal in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8683618307113647,
            "question": "What year did Michael Rich win a gold medal at the Summer Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8216495513916016,
            "question": "Which Olympic Games saw Michael Rich win his gold medal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7901293635368347,
            "question": "What type of cycling event did Michael Rich compete in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.618442714214325,
            "question": "Did Michael Rich win any other medals at the Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5669394135475159,
            "question": "What is Michael Rich known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5399184823036194,
            "question": "Is Michael Rich a famous athlete?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Michael Rich was the gold medalist in the men's team time trial cycling event at the 1992 Summer Olympics.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7365_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Michael Rich known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7365_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Michael Rich win any other medals at the Olympics?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7365_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of cycling event did Michael Rich compete in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7365_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7365_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7365_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7365_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7365_145.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7365_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7365_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7365_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7365_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7365_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7365_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Michael Rich won a gold medal in the men's team time trial (100 km) at the 1992 Summer Olympics, which confirms the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}